IT Specialist	310 Fourth St
Tr Specialise	Riverdale, ND 58565
	Phone: 662.364.0782
	E-mail: joshua.inzer@gmail.com

Summary Statement:

5 years military experience, 11 years of team leadership, 17 years of Information Technology experience. Mission oriented, self-motivated, detail oriented, and strong analytical skills to deliver desired results.

Technical Proficiency

Platforms: Windows OS 98/NT/2000/XP/Vista/7/8/8.1/10/11, Mac OS X, Linux Redhat, Kali Linux, Unix,

Cisco IOS, Apple iOS, Android, Microsoft Server 2003/2008/2012/2016, Microsoft Azure, Solaris

Applications: Unity, Unreal, Autodesk Stingray, Autodesk 3DS, Microsoft Visual Studio, Microsoft Office, Microsoft

365, Adobe Acrobat, Adobe Suite, Microsoft Visio, BeyondTrust, LogMeln, Team Viewer, VMware,

Perforce, Git

Critical Skills: Technical Writing, Time Management, Detail Oriented, Hardware and Software Troubleshooting, Project

Management, Problem Solving, Cisco Systems, Network Security, Installation and Repair, Cable/Electronics, Computer Networking, Aviation Electrician's Certification, 3M Program

Manager/Information System Technician, SAN systems, Blackberry Enterprise Server, AT&T networking

systems, Mobile Armor, Microsoft BitLocker, Retail, Sales

Languages: C#, Python, C++, JavaScript, CSS, XML, HTML, VBS, PHP, SQL

Certifications & Security Clearance rated at **Top Secret, DOD 8570 Compliant**: Clearance's: CompTIA: PenTest+, Security+ CE, Network+, A+, Project+, Data+

ITIL v4, Google: Data Analytics, IT Support Professional, IT Automation with Python

Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) | Software Development Fundamental; Azure Fundamentals; Azure Al Fundamentals; Security, Compliance, and Identity Fundamentals; Azure Virtual Desktop

Specialist; Azure Administrator Associate; Azure Developer Associate

EC-Council Certified Encryption Specialist

ICPM Certified Supervisor

Heron UAV Certified Electronics Technician

Project Experience

2019 - 2021 Office 365 Level 3 Migration Support

Supervisor/Technical Lead

- Responsible for leading a team of a team of seven technicians with reporting and bridging communication between teams, to include Problem Management, Enterprise Service Desk, and Program Management
- Responsible for maintaining troubleshooting guides for Microsoft 365 Applications Office and Teams
- Responsible for maintaining Service Level Requirements
- Responsible for working with Program Management in insuring technicians are trained in troubleshooting all problems arisen throughout migration
- Responsible for ensuring resolution categories are standardized between Program Management, Problem Management, and Enterprise Service Desk

2017 - Present Megaball (3D Rolling Ball Puzzle game)

Team Lead/Lead Programmer/Systems Integration

Responsible for implementing and maintaining system integration and programming standards

- Responsible for maintaining source code health
- Responsible for the troubleshooting and fixing of bugs
- Responsible for ensuring team of four maintained deadlines and code consistency

2004-Present

Tales of Azure Winds (working title, JRPG)

Concept/Story/Lead Designer/Lead Programmer/Producer/ Marketing/Combat System Designer

- Responsible for maintaining Perforce Source Control server and training colleagues on its use, as well as training colleagues on Unity Game Engine and C# language
- Responsible for ensuring game design adheres to games concept
- Responsible for designing and programming Combat, Leveling/Stats, and Inventory Systems

2014-2018

Garrison Dam Network Upgrade

Technician/Consultant

- Responsible for working with district, Garrison Dam Project Office, Network Operation and Security Center (NOSC) personnel to ensure design met customer requirements
- Responsible for liaising between Garrison Dam Project Office, Worldwide Telecom, and NOSC in the implementation of the design for a seamless transition

2015

Ragnarök Chronicles (Tabletop Strategy game) by Twofer Games

Associate Producer

- Responsible for game balancing and original title artwork
- Responsible for team administrative duties as well as Design Document editing

2014

Break the Fate (Tradable card game)

Lead Designer/Producer

- Responsible for design, creation, implementation, and integration of combat system as well as card lore
- Responsible for game balancing to which a zero-sum outcome was possible, but not probable

Work Experience

2021 - Present	SAIC, Riverdale, ND	
	L3 Team Lead – Technician Support IV – US Army Corps of Engineers	
	 Responsible for directing the day-to-day tasks for a team of 7 direct reports and 30 	
	volunteers	
	 Responsible for creating process and procedure ensuring standardization of 300+ PC 	
	technicians, systems administrators, and network administrators	
	 Conduct Windows OS reviews to ensure USACE is compliant with DISA STIGs 	
	 Established Code Review Process to scan for vulnerabilities and other unsecure coding practices 	
	 Listen to customer requirements and translate to actionable tasks 	
	Provide input on modernization of IT services and technology	
2021 - Present	AzureGames, LLC, Riverdale, ND	
	Owner	
	 Created business plan encompassing development 	
	 Ensured all Intellectual Property is copyrighted 	
	 Interface with State government to stay within Good Standing 	
	 Reprioritized 8 ongoing project to be carried out over the next 10 years 	
	 Utilize SCRUM methodology to maintain project management 	
	Leidos, Riverdale, ND	
2018 - 2021	Transition Coordinator	
	 Coordinate with subcontractors to ensure staffing requirements are met 	
	Division Site Supervisor – National Capital Region – US Army Corps of Engineers	
	 Covered the contract services of Field Operations at pivotal Army mission locations at the US 	
	Army Corps of Engineers Headquarters (HQ), Army Geospatial Center (AGC), Humphreys	

Engineer Center Support Activity (HECSA), and 4 Institute for Water Resources (IWR) locations across CONUS

- Responsible for the customer care to 1600+ End User with 80 held at VIP Level of Service
- Supervise and direct the day-to-day actions of 15 technicians and 4 System Administrators
- Provided process improvements to streamline technician workload
- Ensured all sites met Service Level Requirements with an Outstanding rating
- Ensured personnel are compliant with Department of Defense training requirements
- Trained technicians on collaboration tools, resources, and training guides
- Interface with customer to coordinate and execute Temporary Duty Orders

Level 3 Support Technician – US Army Corps of Engineers

- Projects Technical Team Lead
 - Responsible for multiple vendor coordination to maintain US Army Corps of Engineer systems and compliance with Operational Orders (OPORDs)
 - Led teams dedicated to implementation, documentation, and continued maintenance of Microsoft 365 Apps | Office, Teams, OneDrive; Adobe Acrobat DC; Windows 10 | 1709, 1809, 1909; DISA Purebred; Dell | Trusted Platform Module, Command Update, Command Configure
 - Responsible for hosting, answering, and following up with questions asked during Collaboration Calls
 - Responsible for liaising between Field Operations management and Enterprise
 Service Desk and creating process improvements
- Enterprise Service Delivery
 - Consulted with Service Delivery Management to improve upon practices at struggling districts
 - Volunteered and asked to assist multiple districts struggling to meet Service Level Requirements
 - Multitask communication mediums (Email, Jabber, Skype) for PC Technicians who reach out for further assistance of higher tier issues
 - Administered on-site training to junior district technicians on policy and procedures, tech tools, ticket management, and Remedy while assisting technicians in achieving service level requirement

Documentation

- Volunteered and assisted in the updating of the Uniform Installation Procedures to meet customer requirements
- o Created procedures for tools without documentation
- Translated OPORD on US Army Information Systems required naming convention into Standard Operating Procedure for Army Corps of Engineers – Information Technology

PC Naming Tool

- Responsible for liaising between ACE-IT Government Management and Design of PC Naming Tool and ACE-IT Contractor technicians to ensure technicians have access to required resources
- Responsible for ensuring all documentation on tool is current
- Responsible for assisting ACE-IT technicians in troubleshooting the tool

Trainer

- Responsible for administering training to ACE-IT technicians on, but not limited to, PC Naming Tool, FTE tool, Remedy, and Bomgar.
- o Responsible for maintaining training materials are current

Break/Fix Technician – US Army Corps of Engineers

- Responsible for maintaining network communications for US Army Corps of Engineers sites in North Dakota and Montana and repair of computers, switches, and multi-function devices
- Responsible for ensuring all Information Systems (IS) are properly encrypted

	 Consulted with Garrison Dam project management on the physical security and environmental safety of network equipment, physical security of premise, cyber security practices, and personnel safety
2015 - 2018	
	IMRI (Vectrus), Riverdale, ND
	Break/Fix Technician – US Army Corps of Engineers
	 Responsible for maintaining network communications for US Army Corps of Engineers sites in North Dakota and Montana and repair of computers, switches, and multi-function devices Responsible for ensuring all Information Systems (IS) are properly encrypted
2013 - 2015	
	Apex Systems (Lockheed Martin), Riverdale, ND
	Break/Fix Technician – US Army Corps of Engineers
	 Responsible for maintaining a working relationship between ACE-IT and US Army Corps of Engineers employees by performing duties in a professional manner
2012 - 2013	Starkville Computers, Starkville, MS
	Network and Systems Administration/ Technician
	 Responsible for initial configuration, installation, and maintenance of Cisco Switches,
	Microsoft Windows Servers, and Microsoft Windows 7 / 8 computers
2011 - 2012	Rothe Enterprises, Inc., Columbus, MS
	Network Administrator – US Air Force
	 Other areas of concentration included the set up and installation of servers and ensuring back up capability was established, Blackberry Server administration, and VMWare administration
2010 - 2011	Stark Aerospace, Inc., Columbus, MS
	Network Administrator & Heron UAV Electronics Technician
	 Maintained the network, programmed using XML coding style, remote desktop
	troubleshooting, and rewiring were involved
	 Avionics Tech for Unmanned Aerial Vehicle (UAV) included troubleshooting a variety of
	avionics equipment faults, servicing aircraft for flight and post flight, maintained a control
	shelter of computers that linked and controlled the aircraft, maintained, and operated SATCOM and LOS communications
2004 - 2009	United States Navy, San Diego, CA
	Network Administrator & Radio Communication Technician
	 Served as a 3M (maintenance) program manager and supervisor of IT operations while being
	an IT onboard a ship comprised of 4 networks and over 300 computers
	 Served as ship's antenna maintenance officer
	 Served as Technical Support Supervisor to nine technicians
	 Server as Work Center Supervisor to 2 work centers and 22 personnel

Education

2021 - Ongoing	Western Governors University – Bachelor of Science Cybersecurity and Information Assurance
2014 - 2017	Full Sail University – Bachelor of Science in Game Design Winter Park, FL
2008 - 2010	Westwood College Online Bachelor of Science Game Software Development